{
    "subject": "resource/Rio_Tinto_Group",
    "predicate": "ontology/product",
    "object": "resource/Titanium_dioxide",
    "human_readable": "Rio Tinto Group produces Titanium dioxide.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9282753467559814,
            "question": "Does Rio Tinto Group produce any other materials besides Titanium dioxide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7093649506568909,
            "question": "What does Rio Tinto Group produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6397511959075928,
            "question": "How is Titanium dioxide obtained?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5746745467185974,
            "question": "Is Rio Tinto Group involved in the production of chemicals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5397663712501526,
            "question": "Name a product produced by Rio Tinto Group."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5396550297737122,
            "question": "What is Titanium dioxide used for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5184285044670105,
            "question": "What kind of company is Rio Tinto Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49883216619491577,
            "question": "What are some common uses for Titanium dioxide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46236446499824524,
            "question": "What industries rely on Titanium dioxide as a raw material?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03295561671257019,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a material produced by industrial companies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rio Tinto Group produces Titanium dioxide.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7141_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What industries rely on Titanium dioxide as a raw material?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7141_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common uses for Titanium dioxide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7141_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of company is Rio Tinto Group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7141_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_167.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7141_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Rio Tinto Group is involved in producing titanium dioxide. Specifically, document 12 mentions that \"the plant in southwestern Quebec produces steel, scandium and titanium dioxide,\" and document 60 states, \"The plant in southwestern Quebec currently produces steel, scandium and titanium dioxide.\" This confirms that Rio Tinto Group does produce titanium dioxide as part of its operations."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}